Register to The Benny Goodman Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Band and Combo Arrangements
  - NOTHING ("NUTHIN'") Sauter, Eddie (Box 19D, Folder 41)
    BG No.: B262
  - NOW I LAY ME DOWN TO DREAM Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 19D, Folder 42)
    BG No.: B174/401B/10A
  - OBJECT OF MY AFFECTIONS, THE Lipman, Joe, 1934 (Box 19D, Folder 43)
    BG No.: A365/88/7
  - OH BABY! Hensel, Wes, 1961 (Box 19D, Folder 44)
    BG No.: A62
  - OH BABY! Powell, Mel, 2/6/1946 (Box 19D, Folder 45)
    BG No.: B121/35A/90
  - OH BOY Henderson, Fletcher, c.1938 (Box 19D, Folder 46)
    BG No.: A35
  - OH BUT I DO! Todd, Tommy, 1947 (Box 19E, Folder 47)
    BG No.: C150
  - OH BY JINGO Cohn, Al, 1955 (Box 19E, Folder 48)
    BG No.: D69
  - OH GEE! OH JOY! Pierce, Nat, c.1958 (Box 19E, Folder 49)
    BG No.: Al 3/16 9B
  - OH GEE! OH JOY! Williams, George, 6-7/1958 (Box 19E, Folder 50)
    BG No.: A13/169C
    Parts: cl/saxB/tpt/tbn1-3/PGBD/vocal
  - OH GEE! OH JOY! (Box 19E, Folder 51)
    BG No.: A13
  - OH GEE! OH JOY! (Box 19E, Folder 52)
    BG No.: A13/169A
  - OH LOOK AT ME NOW Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 01)
    BG No.: B165/52A
    Also a part labeled "Cootie" for solo trumpet. Complete.
  - OH LOOK AT ME NOW Henderson, Fletcher, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 02)
    BG No.: B165
  - OH LOOK AT ME NOW Siravo, George, 5/1976 (Box 20, Folder 03)
    BG No.: G21
  - OL' PAPPY Bassman, George, 1934 (Box 20, Folder 04)
    BG No.: D15
    Parts: cl/saxT/tpt1-2/tbn1/PBD/banjo
  - OLD INSPECTOR, THE Mersey, Robert, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 05)
    BG No.: B359
  - OLD MAN HARLEM Schutt, Arthur, 1934 (Box 20, Folder 06)
    BG No.: A367/105
  - OLD MAN ROMANCE, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 07)
    BG No.: A364
    Parts: saxBs/tpt1
  - OLD MAN ROMANCE Thompson, Johnny, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 08)
    BG No.: A364/13A
    Parts: cl/saxAATTBs/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGBD
  - OLD MILL STREAM Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 20A, Folder 09)
    BG No.: B175/81
  - ON A CLEAR DAY YOU CAN SEE FOREVER Sauter, Eddie, 12/1965 (Box 20A, Folder 10)
    BG No.: F123
  - ON A LITTLE DREAM RANCH Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 20A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: A363/33/177
  - ON A MISTY NIGHT Dameron, Tadd, 1962 (Box 20A, Folder 12)
    BG No.: G27/263
  - ON A SLOW BOAT TO CHINA Henderson, Fletcher, 1947 (Box 20A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: A97
    Score only in Henderson's own hand. Complete.
  - ON A SLOW BOAT TO CHINA Henderson, Fletcher, 1947 (Box 20A, Folder 14)
    This is a shorter version than the other Henderson arrangement.
  - ON THE ALAMO Burke, Sonny, 1946 (Box 20A, Folder 15)
    BG No.: B122
  - ON THE BEACH AT WAIKIKI Stegmeyer, Bill, 1961 (Box 20B, Folder 16)
    BG No.: D335/60
    Score: missing PP-1-3
  - ONCE UPON A MIDNIGHT Ludlow, Ben, 1935 (Box 20B, Folder 17)
    BG No.: A399/169
  - ONE CIGARETTE FOR TWO Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 20B, Folder 18)
    BG No.: A398
  - ONE DOZEN ROSES Powell, Mel, 1941 (Box 20B, Folder 19)
    BG No.: B192/C370
    Parts: cl/saxATTB(-A2)/tpt1-3/tbn2/PGBD
  - ONE FOR JAY Bunch, John, 1/1963 (Box 20B, Folder 20)
    BG No.: F17/25
    Written for Jay Finegold.
  - ONE FOR MY BABY Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 20B, Folder 21)
    BG No.: B263
  - ONE I LOVE, THE Williams, George, 1958 (Box 20B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: B384/194
  - ONE MORNING IN MAY, 1946 (Box 20C, Folder 23)
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-2/PGBD/horn
  - ONE NOTE SAMBA Karlin, Fred, 1/14/1963 (Box 20C, Folder 24)
    BG No.: F12
  - ONE O'CLOCK JUMP Basie, Count, 1938 (Box 20C, Folder 25)
    BG No.: A277/12
    Also included is a score for brass only showing the addition of tbn3 and the beginning of a tpt4 part. Complete.
  - ONE O'CLOCK JUMP Basie, Count, 1938 (Box 20C, Folder 26)
    BG No.: A277/03/1
    Expanded version of original arrangement. Also included are full set of recopied parts.
  - ONE O'CLOCK JUMP Burns, Ralph (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - ONE SWEET LETTER FROM YOU Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 20D, Folder 27)
    BG No.: A28/132
  - ONE WAY Holman, Bill, 9/1958 (Box 20D, Folder 28)
    BG No.: D205/242
  - ONLY FOREVER Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 20D, Folder 29)
    BG No.: 6A/404B
  - OOH! LOOK-A THERE, AIN'T SHE PRETTY? Henderson, Fletcher, 1947 (Box 20D, Folder 30)
    BG No.: A98/106
  - OOH! WHAT YOU SAID Mundy, Jimmy, 1939 (Box 20D, Folder 31)
    BG No.: B264
  - OPENER Reidy, Frank (Box 20E, Folder 32)
    BG No.: G108/04
    Parts: cl(2)/saxAATTB/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/P(2)GBD
  - OPENING (Box 20E, Folder 33)
    BG No.: F139
    Score: yes (see notes)
    Parts: cl(2)/saxAATTB/tPt3/GBD
    This arrangement is a medley. The score indicates only the transitions between tunes. A guide sheet is included.
  - OPENING Burns, Ralph (Box 33, Folder 01)
  - OPENING FOR SULLIVAN SHOW Sampson, Edgar, 2/1957 (Box 20E, Folder 34)
  - OPUS 1/2 (Box 20E, Folder 35)
    Parts: cl/tbn/PBD
    Later transcription of 1938 "head" arrangement.
  - OPUS I Lipman, Joe, 4/1962 (Box 20F, Folder 38)
    BG No.: G29/266
  - OPUS I Gutesha, Bobby (Box 20E, Folder 36)
    BG No.: D59/232
    Parts: cl/saxTB/tpt/tbn/PGBD
  - OPUS I (Box 20F, Folder 37)
    BG No.: 05
    Parts: saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1-3
    Arrangement recorded by Tommy Dorsey.
  - OPUS LOCAL 802 Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 20F, Folder 39)
    BG No.: 19
  - ORDINARY COUPLE, AN Karlin, Fred, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 01)
    BG No.: D216/19
    B flat version on reverse side of all parts.
  - ORIGINAL Todd, Tommy, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 02)
    BG No.: A397
  - ORIGINAL Todd, Tommy, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 03)
    Score for combo only.
  - ORIGINAL Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 04)
    BG No.: A390
  - ORIGINAL Knight, Peter, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 05)
    BG No.: G24/06
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/PGB
    Clarinet part extends beyond music in score and other parts, but seems to match arrangement.
  - OUR LAST GOODBYE (Box 21, Folder 06)
    BG No.: F130
  - OUT OF NOWHERE Henderson, Fletcher, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 07)
    BG No.: A92/56
    Also included are a complete set of parts in which the sax parts are re-written in the enharmonically equivalent key. Complete.
  - OUT OF THIS WORLD Williams, Mary Lou, 1941 (Box 21A, Folder 08)
    BG No.: B265
  - OUT ON A LIMB Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 21A, Folder 09)
    BG No.: 266
  - OVER THE RAINBOW Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 21A, Folder 10)
    BG No.: A93
  - PADUCAH (#3) Sauter, Eddie, 1943 (Box 21A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: A369
  - PADUCAH (#4) Sauter, Eddie, 1943 (Box 21A, Folder 12)
    Included also sheet of music indicating small changes.
  - PAGE MISS GLORY Murphy, Spud, 8/1935 (Box 21A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: B268/42
  - PAPER MOON Henderson, Fletcher, 1945 (Box 21A, Folder 14)
    BG No.: A127
    Parts: cl(2)/saxAATTB/tpt-4/tbn1-3/PGBD
  - PARATROOPER'S MARCH, THE Engelen, Frank, 1958 (Box 21A, Folder 15)
    BG No.: D46
  - PASSING BY Todd, Tommy, 1947 (Box 21A, Folder 16)
    BG No.: A370
    Also included is a sheet of music indicating small changes.
  - PASTORES, LOS Ogerman, Claus, c.1960 (Box 21A, Folder 17)
    BG No.: G4/L6
  - PEACE BROTHER Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 21A, Folder 18)
    BG No.: A371
  - PENTHOUSE SERENADE Lipman, Joe, 8/25/1962 (Box 21B, Folder 19)
    BG No.: F5
  - PEOPLE WILL SAY WE'RE IN LOVE Sauter, Eddie, 1943 (Box 21B, Folder 20)
    BG No.: B267
  - PERFIDIA Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 21B, Folder 21)
    BG No.: B178/32A
    SaxB/tpt4/tbn3 are not indicated in score. Included are extra parts (C255/45A) for: cl/saxAAT(-T2)/tpt1-3/tbn2/GB. Complete.
  - PERIGRINACION, LA Ogerman, Claus (Box 21B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: G6/L4
  - PERSIAN MARKET Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 21B, Folder 23)
    BG No.: B193
  - PETER PIPER Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 21B, Folder 24)
    BG No.: B82/150
  - PETER'S THEME Sauter, Eddie, 1942 (Box 21B, Folder 25)
    BG No.: A373
    Based on Tchaikovsky's Piano Concerto.
  - PHANTOM OF LOVE Hass, Don, 1982 (Box 21B, Folder 26)
  - PICCOLINO, THE Murphy, Spud, 1935 (Box 21B, Folder 27)
    BG No.: B257
  - PICEROO, 1948 (Box 21C, Folder 28)
    BG No.: 135
  - PINK PANTHER Lipman, Joe, 6/1964 (Box 21C, Folder 29)
    BG No.: F117
  - PIPSQUEAK Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 21C, Folder 30)
  - PLEASE THINK OF ME Kirkpatrick, Don, 1942 (Box 21C, Folder 31)
    BG No.: B266
  - POOR BUTTERFLY Henderson, Fletcher, 1947 (Box 21C, Folder 32)
    BG No.: A99/19
  - POOR LITTLE RICH GIRL Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 21C, Folder 33)
    BG No.: A375/309
    Also included are blank sheets marked tpt4 and tbn3. Complete.
  - POOR LOULIE JEAN Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 21D, Folder 34)
    BG No.: B179/273
  - POPSIE'S IDEA Todd, Tommy, 1947 (Box 21D, Folder 35)
  - POPSIE'S SPECIAL Thompson, Johnny, 1943 (Box 21D, Folder 36)
    BG No.: A374/C311/92A
  - PRETTY BUTTERFLY Giuffre, Jimmy, 1949 (Box 21D, Folder 37)
    BG No.: B81
  - PUT THAT DOWN IN WRITING Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 21D, Folder 38)
    BG No.: C122/214/768
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/PGB
  - QUEER NOTIONS Henderson, Fletcher, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 01)
    BG No.: C5/108/E/178
  - RACHEL'S DREAM Burns, Ralph (Box 33, Folder 07)
  - RACHMANINOFF SPECIAL Powell, Mel, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 02)
    BG No.: C231/80A
  - RADIO MEDLEY Burns, Ralph (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - RAINY BOULEVARD Gutesha, Bobby, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 03)
    BG No.: D56/239
  - RAINY DAY Sawyer, Eddie, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 04)
    Parts: cl1-2/saxT/PGBD
  - RAMONA Sauter, Eddie, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 05)
    BG No.: B1 95
  - RAZE THE RIFF Karlin, Fred, 10/1959 (Box 22, Folder 06)
    BG No.: D83/5
  - RED EYE (Box 22, Folder 07)
    BG No.: D416
    Parts: saxAT/tpt/tbn/GBD(2)
    Marked "for the Norvo Quintet".
  - RED'S SOLO Sampson, Edgar, 1945 (Box 22, Folder 08)
    BG No.: C148/51A
  - REMEMBER Henderson, Fletcher, 1936 (Box 22A, Folder 09)
    BG No.: Y2/139
  - REMEMBER Todd, Tommy, 1947 (Box 22A, Folder 10)
    BG No.: A100
  - RENDEZVOUS TIME IN PAREE Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 22A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: B269
  - RESTLESS Murphy, Spud, 1935 (Box 22A, Folder 12)
    Vocal arrangement. Transcribed, recopied and expanded in 1985 by Sy Johnson for PBS television special.
  - RESTLESS "REVISED" Murphy, Spud, 1935 (Box 22A, Folder 13)
    Parts: cl(3)/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGBD
    This is also adapted by Sy Johnson (see other "Restless" arrangement), only shorter. Clarinet parts include lyrics and sketch sheets.
  - RHYTHM IS OUR BUSINESS Henderson, Fletcher, 1936 (Box 22A, Folder 14)
    BG No.: A45/45/14/100
  - RHYTHM REPEATS Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 22A, Folder 15)
    BG No.: B270
  - RHYTHM STEP, c.1936 (Box 22A, Folder 16)
    BG No.: C149/76/40A
  - RIDIN' HI SHOOTIN' HI MEDLEY Cohn, Al, 5/1962 (Box 22B, Folder 17)
    BG No.: D441/272
    Identical to other "Ridin' Hi ... Medley" only this arrangement modulates to B instead of A at rehearsal letter E.
  - RIDIN' HI SHOOTIN' HI MEDLEY Cohn, Al, 5/1962 (Box 22B, Folder 18)
    Identical to other "Ridin' Hi ... Medley" only this arrangement modulates to A instead of B at rehearsal letter E.
  - RIDIN' HIGH Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 22B, Folder 19)
    BG No.: B242/3/B194
  - RIDIN' HIGH Burns, Ralph (Box 33, Folder 03)
  - RIFF RAFF Karlin, Fred, 10/1959 (Box 22B, Folder 20)
    BG No.: D82/7
  - RIFFIN' AT THE RITZ Miller, Bill, 1936 (Box 22B, Folder 21)
    BG No.: C354/265
    Parts: saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1/G(2)B
    SaxT2 and tpt1 are incomplete.
  - RIFFS Williams, Mary Lou, 1937 (Box 22B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: B271
    Parts: saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn2/GB
  - ROB'T E. LEE Stegmeyer, Bill, 7/1960 (Box 22B, Folder 23)
    BG No.: D327/410
  - ROCK HILL SPECIAL Johnson, Budd, c.1939 (Box 22B, Folder 24)
    BG No.: B280
  - ROCKIN' CHAIR Ludlow, Ben, 1939 (Box 22C, Folder 25)
    BG No.: D21/121
    Parts: saxAT(-A2T2)/tpt1/tbn1-2/B
  - ROCKIN' CHAIR Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 22C, Folder 26)
    Parts: saxAA/tpt1/B
    Parts are in Sauter's own hand.
  - ROCKING THE TOWN Mundy, Jimmy, 1938 (Box 22C, Folder 27)
    BG No.: B279
  - ROCKY RACCOON (Box 22C, Folder 28)
    Parts: cl/saxT/tbn/G
  - ROCKY RACOON, c.1960 (Box 22C, Folder 29)
    BG No.: R2
    Parts: cl/saxAT/tpt1-3/tbn1-2,4/GBD
    Clarinet part serves as condensed score. Also includes insert (R2) marked "on cue". Parts for: saxAATTB/tpt1-2/tbn1-2.
  - RODGERS AND HART MEDLEY (Box 22C, Folder 30)
    BG No.: G11
  - ROMANCE MEDLEY Burns, Ralph (Box 33, Folder 06)
  - ROMEO AND JULIET Ogerman, Claus, c.1969 (Box 22C, Folder 31)
    BG No.: G16
    Parts: cl(4)/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-4/P(2)GBD
  - ROOM WITHOUT WINDOWS Newsom, Tommy, 6/1964 (Box 22C, Folder 32)
    BG No.: F101
  - ROSALIE Clayton, Buck (Box 22D, Folder 33)
    BG No.: B180/251
  - ROSALIE Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 22D, Folder 34)
    BG No.: C275/251
  - ROSE OF THE RIO GRANDE Henderson, Fletcher, 1947 (Box 22D, Folder 35)
    BG No.: A101
  - ROSE OF THE RIO GRANDE (Box 22D, Folder 36)
    BG No.: A101/42
  - ROSETTA Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 22D, Folder 37)
    BG No.: B181/R4/18
  - ROSETTA Henderson, Fletcher (Box 22D, Folder 37A)
  - ROSIE THE RIVETER Sauter, Eddie, 1943 (Box 22D, Folder 38)
    BG No.: D22/125A
    Parts: saxAABs/BD
  - ROSITA, LA Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 22E, Folder 39)
    BG No.: 72A/C235
  - ROYAL GARDEN BLUES Karlin, Fred, 6/15/1960 (Box 22E, Folder 40)
    BG No.: D309"new"/45
  - ROYAL GARDEN BLUES Jenkins, Gordon, 4-5/1976 (Box 22E, Folder 41)
    BG No.: G149
    SaxAA double on clarinet. Photocopies only of: tpt2-4/tbn2-4/GB. Complete.
  - ROYAL GARDEN BLUES Newsom, Tommy, 3/1963 (Box 22E, Folder 42)
    BG No.: D309/23
  - ROYAL GARDEN BLUES Karlin, Fred (Box 22E, Folder 43)
    BG No.: D309/45
    Score: addendum only (see BG no.D309"new"/45 for original)
  - S'POSIN' Henderson, Fletcher, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 01)
    BG No.: D341/126
  - S'WONDERFUL (Box 23, Folder 02)
    BG No.: B378/165
    Different from either Kincaide or Todd scores.
  - S'WONDERFUL Todd, Tommy, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 03)
    BG No.: B378
  - S'WONDERFUL Kincaide, Deane, 4/1958 (Box 23, Folder 04)
    BG No.: B378/G37
    Score: "A" and "B"
    Parts are made from a consolidation of scores A and B. Tpt and rhythm are from A; cl, sax and tpt parts are from B. Complete.
  - S'WONDERFUL "X" Burns, Ralph (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - SAD NIGHT IN HARLEM Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 05)
    BG No.: A230/149/775
    Parts: PB
  - SAINT BERNARD WALTZ O'Farrill, Chico, 1949 (Box 23A, Folder 06)
    BG No.: B103
  - SAINT LOUIS BLUES Henderson, Fletcher, 1936 (Box 23A, Folder 07)
    BG No.: A2/ S1 0/ 17
  - SAINT LOUIS BLUES Hensel, Wes, 1961 (Box 23A, Folder 08)
    BG No.: D412
  - SALUTE TO GLENN MILLER (NEW) Lipman, Joe, 5/1962 (Box 23A, Folder 09)
    BG No.: D439/298
    Medley of: "Moonlight Serenade", "I've Got A Gal In Kalamazoo", "I Know Why", and "Chattanooga Choo-Choo". Complete.
  - SALUTE TO GLENN MILLER (OLD) Lipman, Joe, 5/14/1962 (Box 23A, Folder 10)
    Score: incomplete (pp.12-15 only)
    All parts and score are incomplete, starting at rehearsal no.88.
    For complete arrangement see "Salute to Glenn Miller (New)".
  - SAME TIME TOMORROW Martin, Skip, 1941 (Box 23A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: B218
  - SAN FRANCISCO Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 23B, Folder 12)
    BG No.: A220/135/269
  - SANDMAN Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 23B, Folder 13)
    BG No.: A2 4/ S1 / 6
  - SAVING MYSELF FOR BILL Sauter, Eddie, 1943 (Box 23B, Folder 14)
    BG No.: A223/263
  - SAVING MYSELF FOR YOU Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 23B, Folder 15)
    BG No.: A222/34
  - SAY SI SI (Box 23B, Folder 16)
    BG No.: 89
  - SCARECROW Harding, Buster, 1941 (Box 23B, Folder 17)
    BG No.: A123/32
    All horn parts are manuscript; rhythm parts are from Regent Music Corp. published arrangement.
  - SCATTER BRAIN Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 23B, Folder 18)
    BG No.: C49/94/204
  - SEND IN THE CLOWNS Tunick, Jonathan, 1978 (Box 23B, Folder 19)
    BG No.: G117
  - SENT FOR YOU YESTERDAY Durham, Eddie, 1939 (Box 23C, Folder 20)
    BG No.: C133/48
  - SENTIMENTAL MOOD Kincaide, Deane, c.1955 (Box 23C, Folder 21)
    BG No.: C60
    Score: original and "revoiced" (indicates no tpt or rhythm parts)
    Parts pertain to "revoiced" score. Original score (inc. mixed winds ie. ob/bscl1-2 etc.) indicates tpt and rhythm. Complete.
  - SEPTEMBER SONG Powell, Mel, 1946 (Box 23C, Folder 22)
    BG No.: B393
  - SERENADE IN BLUE, 1941 (Box 23C, Folder 23)
    BG No.: B20/28A/D3
    Parts: saxAAT(-T2)/tpt1-2/tbn1-2/PGBD
  - SERENADE IN BLUE Thompson, Johnny, 1942 (Box 23C, Folder 24)
    BG No.: B20/2A
  - SERENADE TO THE STARS Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 23D, Folder 25)
    BG No.: B49/27
  - SEVEN COME ELEVEN Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 23D, Folder 26)
    BG No.: D26/48A
    Parts: cl/saxAATIB/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGD
  - SEVEN COME ELEVEN (Box 23D, Folder 27)
    BG No.: B24
    Score: incomplete (missing pp.1-2)
  - SEVEN COME ELEVEN Newsom, Tommy, 4/1963 (Box 23D, Folder 28)
    BG No.: D26/5
    Parts: cl/saxTT/tpt/PB
  - SEVEN COME ELEVEN, 1959 (Box 23D, Folder 29)
  - SEVENS WILD Newsom, Tommy, 4/1963 (Box 23D, Folder 30)
    BG No.: F29/18
  - SHAFI Williams, Mary Lou, 1977 (Box 23D, Folder 31)
    BG No.: G136
  - SHAKE DOWN THE STARS Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 23D, Folder 32)
    BG No.: B46/292
    Parts: D
  - SHAME ON YOU Stegmeyer, Bill, 1961 (Box 23E, Folder 33)
    BG No.: D352
  - SHE WORE A YELLOW RIBBON O'Farrill, Chico, 1949 (Box 23E, Folder 34)
    BG No.: C125
  - SHE'S A LATIN FROM MANHATTAN Murphy, Spud, 4/1935 (Box 23E, Folder 35)
    BG No.: B47
  - SHE'S FUNNY THAT WAY Larkins, Ellis; Sampson, Edgar, 1945 (Box 23E, Folder 36)
    BG No.: B123/41
  - SHE'S FUNNY THAT WAY Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 23E, Folder 37)
    BG No.: B1 23/ 100
  - SHINE Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 23E, Folder 38)
    BG No.: C238/33
  - SHINE Clayton, Buck, 1960 (Box 23E, Folder 39)
    BG No.: A7/256
  - SHIRLEY STEPS OUT Powell, Mel, 1947 (Box 23F, Folder 40)
    BG No.: 129
    Parts: saxT/PBD
  - SHIVERS (Box 23F, Folder 41)
    BG No.: D318
    "Head arrangement" transcribed by Bob Wilbur 10/1959. Complete.
  - SHIVERS (Box 23F, Folder 42)
    BG No.: D318/28
  - SHIVERS (Box 23F, Folder 43)
  - SHOO FLY Norman, Fred, 1/30/1956 (Box 23F, Folder 44)
    BG No.: B29/168
  - SHOULD I Henderson, Fletcher, 1946 (Box 23F, Folder 45)
    BG No.: C223/116
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn2-3/PGBD
  - SHOW BILLBOARD Burns, Ralph (Box 34, Folder 02)
  - SHOW ME Casey, Gene, 4/1962 (Box 24, Folder 01)
    BG No.: D430/285
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpti-3/tbn1-2/PGBD
    Vocal arrangement for Joya Sherrill. Includes full set of brass and sax parts which differs slightly at rehearsal letter D.
  - SHOW YOUR LINEN, MISS RICHARDSON Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 02)
    BG No.: A25
  - SHRINE OF SAINT CECELIA Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 03)
    BG No.: B281
  - SIDEWALKS OF CUBA Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 04)
    BG No.: 317/B85
    Tbn3 doubles percussion. Complete.
  - SILHOUETTE Powell, Mel, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 05)
    BG No.: B86/33E
  - SIMPLE AND SWEET Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 06)
    BG No.: B89
  - SING Masso, George, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 07)
    BG No.: G120
    Score: incomplete (pp.1-13 only)
    Parts: cl/saxT/tpt/tbn/PG(2)BD
    Clarinet part is incomplete.
  - SING AN OLD FASHIONED SONG Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 08)
    BG No.: A34/548/21
  - SING FOR YOUR SUPPER Mundy, Jimmy, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 09)
    BG No.: B124
  - SING SING SING, 1959 (Box 24A, Folder 10)
    BG No.: D11/33
  - SING SING SING (Box 24A, Folder 11)
    Parts: saxT/tpt/tbn/D
  - SING SING SING Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 24A, Folder 12)
    BG No.: C212/53
    Parts: saxAAT(-T1)/tpt2-3/tbn1-2
    From 1949 recopy.
  - SING SING SING Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 24A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: C212
    Parts: saxAATTB/tpt1-2(2)3(2)4/tbn1(2)2/PGBD
    Extra tpt and tbn parts are marked S3 and indicate cuts not in other parts. This is a recopy.
  - SING SING SING (PART 1) Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 24A, Folder 14)
    BG No.: S3 (A)
    Parts: cl(3)/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGB
    Includes extra SaxA1 which is slightly different. The extra cl parts serve as condensed scores in B flat transposition.
  - SING SING SING (PART 2) Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 24A, Folder 15)
    BG No.: S3 (B)
    Parts: cl(3)/saxAATTB/tpt1(2)-4/tbn1-3/PGBD
    Makes complete arrangement when combined with "Part 1" (BG no.S3 A).
    Extra cl parts serve as condensed score in B flat transposition.
  - SINGING IN THE RAIN Mundy, Jimmy, 1935 (Box 24B, Folder 16)
    BG No.: 105
  - SIX FLATS UNFURNISHED Maltby, Richard, 1942 (Box 24B, Folder 17)
    BG No.: A88/203
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-2/tbn1-2/PGD
  - SIX LESSONS FROM MADAME LA ZONGA Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 24B, Folder 18)
    BG No.: B88
  - SIXTEEN GOING ON SEVENTEEN Karlin, Fred, 10/31/1959 (Box 24B, Folder 19)
    BG No.: D219/12
  - SKELETON IN THE CLOSET, THE Burns, Ralph, 1947 (Box 24B, Folder 20)
    BG No.: A137
  - SLIPPED DISC (Box 24B, Folder 21)
    BG No.: C232/3
    SaxT doubles flute. Includes parts for "Tag": cl/saxT/tpt/G(2).
  - SLIPPED DISC (Box 24B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: C232
    Parts: saxAAT(-T2)/tpt1/tbn1/PGBD
  - SLIPPED DISC (Box 24C, Folder 23)
    BG No.: C232/103
    Parts: PGBV
  - SLIPPED DISC (Box 24C, Folder 24)
    Parts: cl/tpt/tbn/PBDV
    Tpt part is only a sketch.
  - SLY MONGOOSE Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 24C, Folder 25)
    BG No.: A257
  - SMALL TOWN GIRL Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 24C, Folder 26)
    BG No.: B97/109/30
  - SMALL-FRY Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 24C, Folder 27)
    BG No.: C147/146
    Parts: cl(2)/saxA(2)AAT(2)T(2)/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGB(2)D
  - SMILES Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 24C, Folder 28)
    BG No.: B26/86
  - SMOKE GETS IN YOUR EYES Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 24C, Folder 29)
    BG No.: B217
  - SMOOTH ONE, A Karlin, Fred, 6/161960 (Box 24C, Folder 30)
    BG No.: D310/27
  - SMOOTH ONE, A Karlin, Fred, 5/20/1960 (Box 24C, Folder 31)
  - SMOOTH ONE, A Wilbur, Bob, c.1958 (Box 24C, Folder 32)
    Parts: cl/saxT/tbn/PBDV
  - SMOOTH ONE, A Wilbur, Bob (Box 24C, Folder 33)
  - SMOOTH ONE, A Martin, Skip, 9/13/1941 (Box 24D, Folder 34)
    BG No.: D310/1A
    Tpt4 and tbn3 are added parts. Complete.
  - SO LONG, FAREWELL Karlin, Fred, 10/23/1959 (Box 24D, Folder 35)
    BG No.: D218/13
    SaxAl doubles flute. All parts have taped over corrections. Complete.
  - SO MANY MEMORIES Mundy, Jimmy, 1938 (Box 24D, Folder 36)
    BG No.: A225/37/284
  - SO VERY HAPPY Foster, Frank, 1969 (Box 24D, Folder 37)
    BG No.: G19/S4
    Extra clarinet part serves as condensed score. Complete.
  - SO YOU WON'T SING Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 24D, Folder 38)
    BG No.: B285
  - SOFT AS SPRING Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 24E, Folder 39)
    BG No.: A140/140
    Parts: cl(2)/saxAATTB/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PG(2)BD
  - SOFT WINDS Sauter, Eddie, 1943 (Box 24E, Folder 40)
    BG No.: B27
  - SOFT WINDS (Box 24E, Folder 41)
    BG No.: B27/13
    "Head arrangement" transcribed or notated from performance.
  - SOLITUDE Van Eps, Fred, 1934 (Box 24E, Folder 42)
    BG No.: C380
    Parts: cl/saxAAT(-T2)/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGBD
    Drum part has some music for vibes included.
  - SOLITUDE Van Eps, Fred (Box 24E, Folder 43)
    BG No.: C380/29
    This is an insert to be used with full arrangement. It modulates from D flat to A flat and begins 2 measures before rehearsal letter B.
  - SOLO FLIGHT Mundy, Jimmy, 1941 (Box 24E, Folder 44)
    Also known as "Chonk Charlie Chonk".
  - SOME FUN EH KID Woode, Henri, 1936 (Box 24E, Folder 45)
    BG No.: A226/659
  - SOME OF THESE DAYS Henderson, Fletcher (Box 24F, Folder 46)
    BG No.: B282/8/24/5
    cl/saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/PGBD
    Includes partial set of photocopied parts.
  - SOME OF THESE DAYS Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 24F, Folder 47)
    BG No.: B282
  - SOMEBODY LOVES ME Golson, Benny, 1962 (Box 24F, Folder 48)
    BG No.: B210/206
  - SOMEBODY LOVES ME Henderson, Fletcher, 1936 (Box 24F, Folder 49)
    BG No.: B210
    Score is original; parts are a later recopy. Complete.